So, hello everyone, we are going to work with our chat application in this video, so as
you can see here that this chat application folder has already been made and now inside
of our chat application folder I am going to make two directories, okay, two subdirectories,
so the first one will be for the front end part, so front end and the second one will
be for the back end part, so back end, so for both of these folders we are going to install
set of packages to work with, okay, so what we can do for now is like let's go to this
new terminal, okay, so we are going to install the weed package, okay, so because we are
going to fast, fasten up our process of making like installation and dependencies, so for
that purpose only, so let's change the directory to the front end, so CD front end,
and now since we have changed our path directory to the front end, now we are going
to install the weed, so NPM, create type like this, NPM create weed at the rate of
latest, and since we are going to work in the present directory, so we are going to use
this dot operator, sorry, so it's going to ask like a few bunch of questions, like whether
you want to work in vanilla, VORX, so in our case we are going to work with React,
so we are going to select only this, so after this we are going to select the JavaScript
variant and the rest of the options are default only, so yes, let's scaffolding the project
and installing the dependencies with NPM, and after this it is going to just launch the website,
it is going to launch the React web app, okay, on the local host 5173.